

Cell: 438 401 5640 e-mail: y.bekkali@gmail.com Adress: 2022 Westmore 02 Montreal, Qc H4 B1Z

Linkdin link: https://www.linkedin.com/in/younes-bekkali-90b28594

Profile

A junior developer with a degree and experience in civil engineering, with an understanding of technical concepts and the ability to take new information, with an excellente attitude and with the desire to grow and develop within the role.

Experience

JUNIOR DEVELOPPER, CODEBOXX; MONTREAL, QC - 2020-PRESENT

Weekly tasks either individual or in teams, simulating a real life business situation. Those tasks cover web site development and information systems, and allows the familiarization with API development, Databases, Cloud and covers programming languages such as HTML, Javascript, Python, Go, C# on .NET, Ruby on Rails.

JUNIOR CIVIL ENGINEER, LAKSON INTERNATIONAL INC; MONTREAL, QC - 2015-2109

Completes a variety of assignments, drawings, specifications, and materials suitable for procurement and construction proposes. Prepares standard engineering computations, material quality takeoffs, estimates, surveys, and designs. Provides input and technical guidance to CAD Designer/Drafters. Occasionally prepares and develops fully coordinated construction drawings and installation prints as a final deliverable for clients.

BIM / CAD DESIGNER, LAKSON INTERNATIONAL INC; MONTREAL, QC - 2007-2014

Coordinates building information models (BIM) between disciplines. Assistes all departments in generating technical and construction drawings, BIM development, Clash detection, 4D simulations, 5D quantity surveys, and traditional estimating. Develops and maintains company AutoCAD & Revit standards and templates.

PROJECT COORDINATOR, BMA INTERNATIONAL; BRAUNSCHWEIG, GERMANY – 2004-2006 Participates in construction surveillance and components assembly control of the international sugar factories projects. Benchmarking, Quality Control..

AUTOMATION & CONTROL AGENT, COSUMAR ONA-GROUP; CASABLANCA, MA – 2002-2004

Programs PLC's and distributed control systems. Installs, configures and calibrates digital sensors (limit switches, photo eyes, proximity switches, etc.), analog sensors (flow, pressure, temp, distance, laser, sonic, radar, etc.), special/safety sensors (light curtains, area scanners, bar code readers)



Cell: 438 401 5640 e-mail: y.bekkali@gmail.com Adress: 2022 Westmore 02 Montreal, Qc H4 B1Z

Linkdin link: https://www.linkedin.com/in/younes-bekkali-90b28594

Education

Codeboxx Technology School , Montreal, QC – Junior Developer, 2020

Ecole de Technologie Superieure, Montreal, QC – Graduate Degree in Projects in Construction Engineering and Management, 2016

Polytechnique Montreal, Montreal, QC - Bachelor's Degree in Civil Engineering, 2014

Faculty des Sciences et des Technologies , Fez, MA - Bachelor's Degree in Electrical Engineering: Networks & Telecommunication, 2003

Skills

Problem Solving - Tackle both large conceptual level and task level problems.

Adaptability - able to jump from project to project and stay abreast of all changes.

Communication - able to discern the meaning of what other professionals are saying (and describing) and also present information in a way that can be thoroughly considered and understood.